Contact

nguyenbehanh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hannahnguyen-27a75676 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Social Design
UI/UX
Branding & Identity

Languages

Chinese (Professional Working) Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Hannah Nguyen

Graphic - Web - UI/UX Designer Vietnam

Summary

With more than 8 years experience as a Graphic and UI/UX designer, I have successfully managed and coordinated graphic design projects from concept through completion. Work closely with clients to create vision, conceive designs, and consistently meet deadlines and requirements.

I have expertise in creative direction, web design, branding and identity, user experience and user interface design and development. I can work with various tools and frameworks, such as Figma, XD, InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap.

Effectively build, motivate, direct design and production team. Coordinate freelance designers, consultants and vendors to meet all project requirements. Expertly convert features into benefits to achieve client objectives.

As an experienced professional designer, I would like to utilize my earlier experience and knowledge for designing, developing and taking important decisions in the favor of the company.

Taking important decisions promptly would lead to the advancement and progress of the company.

Experience

Global Performance Commerce Lead Graphic Designer/ UI UX Designer April 2019 - Present (6 years) Vietnam

I've been working on 2 main fields Graphic design and UI/UX Design: GRAPHIC DESIGN:

 Creating more than 100+ visual elements used across our web properties and all other digital formats.

- Designing more than 30+ branding logos and multiple printing products. (POSM, Brochure, Catalogue,...)
- Designing more than 100+ social posts banners.

UI/UX DESIGN:

- Work under the Art Director to produce high-quality UX design solutions through wireframes, visual and graphic designs, flow diagrams, storyboards, site maps, and prototypes to accurately convey project plans to art director, internal staff, and external support partners.
- Design graphic user interface elements, like menus, tabs, and widgets for digital assets.
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look.
- Discovering new projects, understanding the pain points and users' expectations, and defining how to approach the problems or innovations through user experience.
- Creating the key visual and layout for more than 50+ websites.
- Conceptualize, design, and specify UX and UI for more than 20+ mobile applications to effectively organize, convey and present text and graphics as required.

LEADERSHIP:

Vietnam

- My main responsibility is upgrading my skills and convey the knowledge to the other members.
- Ensure all projects are on schedule.

Next Future Co., Ltd Senior Graphic - UI/UX designer August 2017 - February 2019 (1 year 7 months)

My company is an agency so I've worked on more than 50+ variety projects: GRAPHIC DESIGN:

- Working closely with manager, clients, suppliers to create vision, conceive designs, and consistently.
- Processing monitoring from designing period to printing period, quality assurance for final product. (brochure, profile, folder, leaflet...)

WEBSITE - UI/UX DESIGNER:

- Creating PSD template/HTML/CSS layouts for our company and clients.

- Researching UI/ UX and corporate with development team to make the websites to be launched.

ICONIC Co., Ltd.

Senior Graphic Web Designer

February 2012 - July 2017 (5 years 6 months)

Vietnam

Design websites and print ads (leaflet, handbook, brochure, namecard, calendar, banners, advertisement), POSM...

- ITWorks website and print ads
- Iconicjob websites
- Website and Branding identity for Beneflex service
- POSM for fair in Japan
- Company profiles for Nissan, NGK, Iconc

. . . .

XTAsea

Web designer (Online working style) January 2011 - January 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Vietnam

A. Design websites:

Xtasea.com XTAsea web solutions

Riva-yacht Pershing-yacht Ferriti-yacht Yohananof

B. Print ads:

Logo Leadyou

Bloom brand communications

Graphic Designer

January 2011 - January 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Vietnam

B. Print ads:

Logo Leadyou

MHB bank (CEO story profile)

S-Dragon (Logo and Guideline)

Sao Mai hotel (Chrismast background)

Blue moon hotel Brochure

Tai Tai company (Design folder and package)

. . .

Novafusion company Intership Graphic Designer September 2011 - December 2011 (4 months) Vietnam

Wellcome Mart: Designed Print Ad for New year eve event.

Lotte Mart: Retouching product's images.

Education

Van Lang University
Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design · (2007 - 2011)

Thai Phien

Chinese Studies · (2006 - 2010)